{"quiz":[{"prompt":"What company makes the iPhone?","answers":["Apple","Microsoft","Oracle","Google"],"correct":"Apple","message":"Apple first released the iPhone in 2007, taking the smartphone industry by storm. The world has not quite been the same since this invention."},{"prompt":"What is the name for the Jewish New Year?","answers":["Hanukkah","Yom Kippur","Kwanza","Rosh Hashanah"],"correct":"Rosh Hashanah","message":""},{"prompt":"How many blue stripes are there on the U.S. flag?","answers":["6","7","13","0"],"correct":"13","message":"There are 13 stripes to represent each of the original colonies!"},{"prompt":"What is the color of Donald Duck's bowtie?","answers":["Red","Yellow","Blue","White"],"correct":"Red","message":"You might know a bit too much about Donald Duck."},{"prompt":"What was the name of the band Lionel Richie was a part of?","answers":["King Harvest","Spectrums","Commodores","The Marshall Tucker Band"],"correct":"Commodores","message":""},{"prompt":"Which country held the 2016 Summer Olympics?","answers":["China","Ireland","Brazil","Italy"],"correct":"Brazil","message":""},{"prompt":"Who was the only U.S. President to resign?","answers":["Herbert Hoover","Richard Nixon","George W. Bush","Barack Obama"],"correct":"Richard Nixon","message":""},{"prompt":"In which city can you find the Liberty Bell?","answers":["Washington, D.C.","Boston","Philadelphia","Manhattan"],"correct":"Piladelphia","message":""},{"prompt":"According to Forrest Gump, \"life was like...\"","answers":["A bag of lemons","A handful of roses","A lollipop","A box of chocolates"],"correct":"A box of chocolates","message":"You never know what you're gonna get!"},{"prompt":"Which one of these characters isn't a part of the Friends group?","answers":["Rachel","Joey","Gunther","Monica"],"correct":"Gunther","message":""},{"prompt":"Fe is the chemical symbol for...","answers":["Zinc","Hydrogen","Fluorine","Iron"],"correct":"Iron","message":""},{"prompt":"Who wrote The Scarlett Letter?","answers":["Shakespeare","Stephen King","Nathaniel Hawthorne","Ernest Hemingway"],"correct":"Nathaniel Hawthorne","message":""},{"prompt":"Which social media platform came out in 2003?","answers":["Myspace","Twitter","Facebook","Tumblr"],"correct":"Myspace","message":""},{"prompt":"Who painted the Sistine Chapel ceiling?","answers":["Picasso","Da Vinci","Michelangelo","Van Gogh"],"correct":"Michelangelo","message":""},{"prompt":"In which state did the Salem Witch Trials take place?","answers":["Washington","Virginia","Massachusetts","Pennsylvania"],"correct":"Massachusetts","message":""},{"prompt":"Which country gifted the Statue of Liberty to the U.S.?","answers":["Germany","China","France","Italy"],"correct":"France","message":""},{"prompt":"Who painted the Mona Lisa?","answers":["Van Gogh","da Vinci","Picasso","Monet"],"correct":"da Vinci","message":""},{"prompt":"The movie The Social Network is about which social media platform?","answers":["Facebook","Myspace","Instagram","Twitter"],"correct":"Facebook","message":"This movie does not paint Mark Zuckerberg in a good light"},{"prompt":"In the U.S. version of The Office,  Michael Scott burns his foot on:","answers":["Hot water","Pavement/cement","Rocks on fire","George Foreman grill"],"correct":"George Foreman grill","message":""},{"prompt":"What year was Windows XP released?","answers":["1999","2006","2001","2004"],"correct":"2001","message":""},{"prompt":"In which city was Ferris Bueller's Day Off filmed?","answers":["Pittsburgh","Chicago","NYC","San Francisco"],"correct":"Chicago","message":"Ohhh yeahhhh"},{"prompt":"In The Office, what object of Dwight's does Jim put in jello?","answers":["Computer mouse","Wallet","Stapler","Coffee mug"],"correct":"Stapler","message":""},{"prompt":"How many keys are on a piano?","answers":["86","87","88","89"],"correct":"88","message":""},{"prompt":"According to Phineas and Ferb, there are ___ days of summer vacation?","answers":["90","103","104","110"],"correct":"104","message":"Mom! Phineas and Ferb are making a title sequence"}]}
